export let questions = [
    {
        question: 'This is the question 1',
        options: ['Option 1.','Option 2.', 'Option 3.'],
        answer: 'Option 1.'
    },

    {
        question: 'This is the question 2',
        options: ['Option 1.','Option 2.', 'Option 3.'],
        answer: 'Option 2.'
    },

    {
        question: 'This is the question 3',
        options: ['Option 1.','Option 2.', 'Option 3.'],
        answer: 'Option 3.'
    },
    
    {
        question: 'This is the question 4',
        options: ['Option 1.','Option 2.', 'Option 3.'],
        answer: 'Option 1.'
    },

    {
        question: 'This is the question 5',
        options: ['Option 1.','Option 2.', 'Option 3.'],
        answer: 'Option 2.'
    },

    {
        question: 'This is the question 6',
        options: ['Option 1.','Option 2.', 'Option 3.'],
        answer: 'Option 3.'
    },

    {
        question: 'This is the question 7',
        options: ['Option 1.','Option 2.', 'Option 3.'],
        answer: 'Option 1.'
    },

    {
        question: 'This is the question 8',
        options: ['Option 1.','Option 2.', 'Option 3.'],
        answer: 'option 2 !'
    },

    {
        question: 'This is the question 9',
        options: ['Option 1.','Option 2.', 'Option 3.'],
        answer: 'Option 3.'
    },

    {
        question: 'This is the question 10',
        options: ['Option 1.','Option 2.', 'Option 3.'],
        answer: 'Option 1.'
    }
]